As you know, there's always more changes that we wish
we could do, if we just had a little more time.
We're going to leave those as exercises to you, if you want to
keep polishing up. For example, for simplicity, we had all tablet
sizes and orientations use the same layout. However, 7 inch portrait
would actually look better as a one pin UI. So you
can modify your resource folders to make 7 inch portrait use
the phone layout. You can also tweak the two pane behavior
so that the today layout is auto selected when you first launch the
app. Also, this should just say today instead of having the full date. That
way, it'll look more like the other items. As you play around with the
app, feel free to make changes you think would help improve the user experience.